thebobs.com 2010-11-22

# The BOBs - Deutsche Welle - Privacy

### Privacy Information

We are especially concerned about protecting your privacy. For that reason, we wish to make clear what data is collected during your visit to our site and how it will be used.

**Personal data**

Personal data is specific information about the personal or business relationships of a distinct or ascertainable individual. This includes information such as your actual name, address, telephone number and date of birth. Information that has no direct connection to your actual identity, such as your favorite websites or the number of users on a page, is not considered personal data.

**Collection of personal data**

Personal data will only be saved if you provided the information yourself (see below). In addition to the personal data you provide, the following access information will be temporarily stored for the duration of a visit:

\- the pages you have visited  
\- the page from which you visit us  
\- the date, time and duration of a page view  
\- the amount of data transferred  
\- the access status  
\- a description of the Web browser and operating system being used to visit the site   
\- the IP address and computer name (connection data of the inquiring computer)

Additional personal information including:

\- your name  
\- your address  
\- your telephone or  
\- e-mail address

will not be collected unless you have voluntarily provided it in the context of, for example, suggesting a site for nomination or signing up for the user voting lottery.

**Use and dissemination of private data**

The personal data made available by a user will be used exclusively for the purpose of the technical administration of the website and the fulfillment of your wishes and requests. Your personal information will not be distributed, sold or otherwise transmitted to third parties for commercial or advertising purposes. 

**Use of Cookies**

In general, cookies serve the purpose of reminding a site's provider of who your are. Cookies are small bits of data on your computer (a text file with numeric codes) that are sent from a Web server to your browser and saved on your hard drive. You have the possibility to adjust your browser settings to receive an alert when a cookie has been received. That gives you the choice of deciding whether you want to accept the cookie or not.

Our websites generally do not make use of cookies. Only in exceptional cases do we use so-called session cookies. Session cookies only exist for the duration of a visit and only save the data in a Web browser that are necessary to technically facilitate a visit. These data are not personal and are deleted upon closure of the browser.

**Security**

We strive to meet all the technical and organizational security measures required to protect your personal data from loss or abuse. All personal data is stored in a secure operating environment that is not accessible to the public.

**Additional Information**

If you have questions concerning the processing of your personal data, you can contact us, including in cases when you are looking for information or have comments or criticism. 

Upon submission of a written inquiry, we will inform you which data about you (such as name or address, etc.) has been saved. You have the opportunity to submit a written request for the deletion of any user data pertaining to you that we have saved.

**Contacting the editors**

If you have any additional questions about this privacy statement or about "The BOBS Awards" in general, feel free to contact us via our contact form.

You can also contact us by mail at:

Deutsche Welle  
DW-WORLD / "The BOBs"  
D-53110 Bonn  
Germany
